Is this Colin? How's it going? Nice to
MEET YOU. THIS IS YOUR [screaming]
MILLION DOLLARS.
>> After all that happened, the number one
question I kept getting, of course, was,
"How do you solve a million-dollar
puzzle? What was the final solution? And
why was the vault code R62 L3905 L7362
3093123
0. So, initially, I decided I would make
a series of walkthrough videos to go
through all the details. I started
making a video that just focused on the
first nine puzzles, which were
technically optional to solve in case
you hear me refer to them later as phase
zero. And these nine puzzles were some
of my favorites because they were in a
popular puzzle hunt style that I like to
describe with three steps: exploration,
execution, and extraction. Since this is
just how I like to think about puzzle
hunts, I'll say a little bit about what
each of those steps means. Exploration
is just finding patterns and recognizing
what type of puzzle you're looking at.
Execution is the fun part. It's where
all the work happens. It's what most
people generally associate with a
puzzle. Putting together a jigsaw,
filling in a cross word, doing a maze.
Extraction is really the unique step
that I think is most strongly tied to
the puzzle hunt format. And that's
finding or otherwise decoding the answer
to the puzzle, a secret word or phrase.
It can get pretty creative, but very
often it involves indexing, which means
using numbers as positions in words. So
if I have the word fox and the number
three, I can combine them to take the
third letter x. Another very common
technique is to get letters from numbers
directly by using alpha numeric where 1
is a, two is b, three is c, and so on
all the way down to 26 which is z.
Anyway, I finished a video for the first
nine puzzles and then I learned that Mr.
Beast was also planning to do the same
thing. So naturally, I put my project on
the back burner. And if you're watching
this, then Mr. Beast has released what
is probably the coolest and craziest
puzzle breakdown of all time, and I will
link it in the description. He covers so
much that I don't really feel an
incentive to duplicate all that content
in a different voice. However, when I
made that video, I wanted to describe
the process and approach to this hobby
as best I could, so you could see
yourself figuring everything out and
enjoying it in the way I think so many
people did. And because of the puzzle
hunt style I'm mentioning, there ended
up being a lot of leftover value in my
opinion for that specific set of intro
puzzles that I think Mr. Beast couldn't
really go into without starting a show
called Beast Puzzle Games. So, this is
an abridged version of a video I almost
scrapped, a detailed walkthrough of how
to begin solving the Million-Dollar
Puzzle. Feel free to leave comments and
especially questions about these in
later puzzles if there's enough
feedback. I think it'd be fun to cover
any remaining minutia on Twitch and
present my team's worksheet and or a
really nice writeup that I know is out
there from another team with their
permission. And now here's me casually
streaming puzzles from a hotel room. I
should warn you that the production
qualities, where was I? Million-dollar
playlist, nine videos, nine image links.
Most of the image links are now dead,
but early on a Reddit user collected all
of the puzzles and put them in the Mr.
Beast subreddit. So, here they are. You
can print them out. They're most of them
work very well as pen and paper puzzles,
and they're fun that way. So, if they
look fun to you, uh, go ahead and try
that. But what you just saw is the
entirety of phase zero. And this is
going to be the first puzzle, 100 Wells
in Africa. This is a word search. And
it's unconventional, obviously, because
of all the water in the grid, but also
instead of a plain word list, we have
clues. And it might feel natural to try
and answer the clues and then find those
words in the grid, but as you look at
them, they're too vague to answer in
most cases. So, a type of boat, a US
landmark, these are not specific enough
to get good answers to. So, I found it
easier to look at the grid blindly and
find words and then go back to the clues
and see if I could relate them to find
out what was going on here. There's
definitely a level of trust you have to
have with puzzle hunts in that the
designers want you to have fun. Things
are not as random as they seem. Usually,
there's a theme or something secret
going on that's going to form a pattern
and tie it all together. So, when I
looked at the grid, I found robin on
this diagonal, wink, crossing robin, and
train in the upper right hand corner.
There are a few other red herring words
in the grid, but these are the ones that
are going to be helpful. So, for me,
coming back to the clues, I saw a
literary outlaw, two words, and thought
of Robin Hood. And then I looked back at
Robin and asked, well, where's Hood? Why
is that not in the grid? And there is a
letter D after this water droplet that's
sort of in the way. I had a thought
there, but I wanted to confirm it. And I
went to work with train. The train
worked as a child's toy, but it says
it's two words and hyphenated. So to
make it a little bit longer, you can
think of choo choo train. And that
pretty much makes the pattern here,
which is that water in the grid
represents the letters H O. And if you
ask why, if you haven't thought of it
already, that's because the chemical
formula for water is H2O. And yes, it's
two H's and one O, not one H and two
O's. Don't think about it too hard.
They're just being funny. Wink is a
little bit trickier, but that ends up
being hoodwink for deceive. And so on.
and you can find a word that contains
the letters H O for every clue and then
find those all in the grid. So, this is
the final word list. I've gone ahead and
marked all of the words in the grid in
green. And I've also circled the only
two water droplets that weren't used in
red because they're about to be
important. Some of the more interesting
clues were a cold noise, meaning a noise
you make when you have a cold. Uh, hooer
was definitely a Google for me. That
just means anyone from the state of
Indiana. shook took me a minute just
because not only is it slang, but it has
the fewest letters. So, there's only two
other letters in the grid to find here
on the bottom row. And then I think the
last ones I got were definitely hurray
because you also have woohoo as an
option and a foui, which I knew from
Donald Duck, but I think I had something
written down like shoot. It really
helped to eliminate other words from the
grid. Exploration was figuring out that
this was a word search and that there
was a theme with the clues. execution
was finding all of the words. And now
it's time for extraction. In this case,
there are two sets of unused information
from this puzzle. The more obvious one
is all of the unused letters in the
grid. So reading those off, you get
count H2O into each word. That's where
the droplets I've circled in red come
in. They represent the number two in
H2O. And that's actually a hint for what
we're going to do next, which is
indexing the number of water droplets
into the words that contain them. So the
very first clue, a chew, it reads up
here in this column, and it has one
water droplet. So that's going to be the
number one. And the first letter is a.
It's the same for Robin Hood. Robin
Hood, if you recall, had one water
droplet. So that's going to be a one,
which is the first letter R. And I've
covered it on the grid here, but there
is a plus sign in the bottom rightmost
set of water droplets. And that's
because in Choo Choo Train, you have two
sets of water and they have to be added
together 6 plus 6 to make 12. So the
12th letter of Choo Choo Train is I.
And this is the full list of indexes and
it reads out answer is every. So the
answer to the first puzzle is just the
word every. Moving on to puzzle number
two, changing the lives of 600
strangers. This one is a sudoku. If you
haven't seen a sudoku before, they
contain the numbers 1 through nine once
in every row, column, and 3x3 box. So,
for this puzzle, the numbers 1 through
nine have been replaced by nine letters
given in the bottom right of the puzzle
in blue. And I won't solve the whole
puzzle in this video, but early on there
is a pretty difficult step that I wanted
to go over. And it's after you put in
the letter C and the letter N into the
grid, you have to look at the letters A
and H. So this A right here blocks an A
from these two squares in the upper
right box of the grid. So I'm going to
put an A in these two and lowerase to
indicate it has to be in one of these
two squares.
Similarly, the letter L here is blocked
from those two squares. So, these two
squares have to be the letters A and L.
And the only two letters missing from
this whole box are E and H,
which is going to come in handy in a
moment. And so, the first thing to do
with this information is look at the
second column. And an A cannot be in
this cell because of these. An A cannot
be in this cell. So the only box left
for an A in the second column is this
right here. And next I'm going to look
at the letter H. So these cells cannot
be H's. And we have an H that has to be
in one of these two cells in the upper
middle box because of the rest here. You
can't have an H here. You can't have an
H here. So there has to be an H in one
of these two cells. And now if I ask
where can an H be in the second row, it
can't be anywhere in here because of
this. It can't be anywhere in here. And
there's an H blocking this cell. So this
cell has to be an H. And from there, I
think the Sudoku gets pretty solvable.
But that definitely took me a minute.
Here is the final solution to the
Sudoku. And the extraction is pretty
tricky. You have to actually pay
attention at the beginning before you
start solving that the letters given to
you are in this checkerboard pattern
here.
And the answer to the puzzle is in these
missing checkerboard cells. And on the
right in my sheet, you can see that the
answer is going to be the word
challenge. Puzzle number three. I'm
going to have to start being faster with
these. This one is referencing a list of
TV shows on the left. And on the right,
we have more crossword clues like in the
first puzzle. Here, you just want to try
and answer as many clues as you possibly
can to try and find the pattern between
them. The debris at the top isn't really
helpful until later. The starting point
they set up for you here is pretty cool.
It's third to last row where the reality
show being referenced is the Beast
Games. And Jimmy and Mark's Ocean
Charity is in the title of the puzzle,
Team C's. And the thing to notice here
is that all of the letters in Team C's
are also in Beast Games with the
exception of the capital B and the
capital G. The capitals are irrelevant,
but it in my opinion, it just makes it
very easy to notice this. [laughter]
It's me, Dr. Xnore. And in my opinion,
your opinion is bad. The first letters
are very relevant. Every show is two
words. The first letters are what make
the difference between the clue words.
And they even call it initial removed
debris. I don't know how I didn't see
that before. Carry on. And I think the
next one I used to confir
>> No, no, wait. I'm not done. What's crazy
is in two puzzles from now, I'm going to
say something along the lines of you
should always try more specific ideas
before general ones. What an imbeel.
What an ultra maroon. It was opera
paired with top gear. And then anything
that takes up space is matter which goes
with get smart. Each of these TV shows
needs to lose exactly two letters to
become one of the words on the right
side. The research is definitely
difficult. The internet movie database
IMDb is going to be your best friend
here. And towards the end, you can use
the debris to try and take letters away
from any extra TV shows you have or add
letters to any of the clues that you
have to try and make the last few pairs
work. I kind of just ignored the numbers
on the right hand side of the puzzle at
the beginning, you can try a few things
with them. But when nothing really works
out and you have other work to do, uh,
you should go do that work. Each of
those pairs of numbers is used to index
into the TV shows on the left hand side.
And to get the order, you have to notice
that the TV shows are in alphabetical
order by genre, starting with A for
action and going to S for superhero. And
that indicates that the clues on the
right hand side, which are sort of in an
unpredictable order, are the order that
you need to use. So here is the final
list of TV shows and words. I've kept
the original order of the words and
reordered the shows to match them. What
if has six letters and if you remove IW,
you get all of the letters in half. And
then the numbers for that clue axis
handle are three and four. I go back to
the TV show and take the third and
fourth letters A and T. I read this all
the way down and I get a term for chief
roles which is leads or metals with
symbol PB which is leads. So the answer
is leads or leads L E A Ds. Next up, the
first puzzle I cannot take credit for
directly. Number four is $1 to $500,000
experiences. And the flavor text at the
top says, "Where did I go?" This puzzle
is a geography puzzle. The rectangles
are meant to look like street signs. And
so what's going on here is they've taken
two street signs and overlapped them. So
it's kind of like you're looking at one
letter through the stencil or outline of
the other letter. I was glad someone
else did this. It's a little bit of a
headache to look at these colors and
strange shapes for too long. The goal is
to get two words out of each rectangle.
So the very one at the top in red is
Danesberry and Glen Karen if I'm
pronouncing those right. You want to
sort all of these signs in rainbow
order. And then of course the question
is how do I extract the answer? I
imagine once you have all the locations
of one color, you do a little bit of
digging and write down where the
intersection of those streets is, what
city, what county, what municipality,
what state, province and country. And
the pattern ends up being in the city
names. The first three in red are
located in Toronto, Toledo, and Tempe.
The next three orange intersections are
located in Owensboro, Ottawa, and
Orlando. And all three of the cities
start with the same letter. So these
start with W, A, R, D, S. The answer to
puzzle number four is tors. Number five,
Pokémon Go stereotypes. Each of the cage
bars at the bottom has a number in it.
And Pokemon have a unique ID. And when
you look up these Pokemon, they each fit
very nicely into their respective boxes.
So the task here is to put the cage bars
in the grid to form a cage that is a
loop around the little man in the grid.
The second assumption to make is that
the blue boxes are intersections of the
clues. Without that, I think there is
too much to work with. With puzzles like
this, you always want to try specific
ideas before more general ones just to
see if they work. This is the amount of
progress I made using just logic without
any guessing whatsoever. The way you get
these pieces is first by finding letters
that only occur twice. So, the letter A
is only in one down clue and one across
clue. So, you know, those have to be put
together that way. W Trio is interesting
because we're not playing Scrabble. We
don't want to form new words other than
the Pokemon. So, we shouldn't have any 2
by twos. And that means that in order to
have an I and an O intersect next to
each other, one word has to end in I and
the other start with O, or one word has
to start with I and the other one has to
end with O. And this is the only unique
way to do that. And lastly, there are
two down clues that have three blue
boxes. and two across clues that only
have one blue box. So those are like
branches on the loop and those end up
being very unique, easy connections to
make. From there, you want to put all
the pieces together and this is the
final solution. It's the first one I
got. I don't know if there are others
that maybe don't fit in the grid and you
have to do it again. I took a couple of
guesses and this is what I got. And I
can prove that this is the correct
solution by copying the format of the
grid where that red square is the little
man
and pasting that here. The red square is
indeed inside the loop of words that I
have made. And now to get the answer is
a little bit tricky, but as long as
you've kept the blue boxes around, they
are what you need to look at. The weird
thing is you're not reading in a loop or
even left, right, top to bottom. There
are sort of two columns here. So if you
start with this S in the top left and
read downwards, you can see the word
solution and then the I jumps to the S
at the top of the puzzle again for
solution is location. So location is the
answer to puzzle number five. Puzzle
number six is a standard logic puzzle
called tents. In this case, the rules
are written at the top of the puzzle.
The goal is to place one tent next to
each tree such that no tents touch even
diagonally. One thing to be careful of
is that even though there's only one
tent per tree, a tree is allowed to be
next to multiple tents and a tent is
allowed to be next to multiple trees.
The numbers on the outside of the grid
also indicate how many tents are in each
row and column. The numbers inside the
grid are unusual, but they just
represent all of the possible places
tents can be. And so solving this puzzle
means you're figuring out which of the
digits inside the grid are relevant to
the final answer. Getting started with
this puzzle was pretty tricky. What I
did was look at the two rightmost
columns and they can only have four
tents in them. And in the rightmost
column, just the one, there are four
trees. So all four of the tents here are
really assigned to these four trees. So
any other possible tents have to be
marked impossible. And that's these gray
squares right here.
Similarly on the left side, five columns
have 9/10 in them, but the first four
columns have nine trees. So the 9/10 of
those nine trees encompass all five
columns. And so all of the extra squares
can be marked as not having a tent. And
that is enough to really get you
started. After a little bit of work,
there was another sticking point that I
thought was kind of interesting. And so
in this column right here, there are
supposed to be three tents. You can
pretty easily get these two. And the
third one is going to be on either side
of this tree. You don't know where, but
you know that the third one is there.
And that actually eliminates a tent from
being in any of these locations.
And in the column to the left, you're
looking for two tents. One of them is
here. Another one is here. And that lets
you mark this square as not having a
tent in it, which allows you to figure
out that the tent to this tree is placed
to its right. The rest of the puzzle
wasn't too bad in my opinion. This is
where all of the tents are located. And
the extraction is a little bit
different. And it turns out that the
digits in each row and column sum to
numbers between 1 and 26. I originally
only figured out the rows and after a
while of looking at quartet after pen
and not feeling like I could get a
straight answer from that. That was when
I also tried the columns. And that's
what's pretty interesting about this is
it's not trivial to make that work out.
I think it's pretty cool that they did
that that the same numbers can be added
in both directions to give different
correct letters. So the final clue
phrase is quartet after pen brand last
or user. And the word that can come
after all of those four words is name.
So the answer to puzzle six is name.
Puzzle number seven. I adopted 100 dogs.
This puzzle looks like busy work because
it is busy work. There's not much way
around the spot the difference piece of
this. You're just going to have to go
through every dog and answer all five
questions. I found it much quicker
rather than to go one dog at a time to
go one question at a time. So here in my
sheet, I made five grids where I
answered each question yes or no with a
quick one or zero. And then in the
bottom right, I wrote a quick formula to
concatenate all the ones and zeros into
five-digit codes. So that brings me to
the difficult part of this puzzle, which
is actually decoding what letter each
dog stands for. We've been given this
sort of ven diagram with five ovals. And
because the L is in the center, that
means dogs that answer every question,
yes, represent the letter L. You could
probably go to a cryptogram solver or
ask AI to help you with this step, but I
took the cryptography approach. If
you've never tried to decode a cipher
before, I think the first rule of thumb
to know is that E is by far and away the
most common letter of the English
alphabet. In this case, it's also useful
that E happens to be in one of the five
locations that represents an
intersection of four out of the five
ovals.
So, I wrote down all of the codes that
had four ones and one zero and counted
them up. The last one where the dogs
answer yes to every question except
who's wiggling their tail is by far the
most common. So I assigned that one to
the letter E. And because the fifth
question was answered no, the letter E
is not in this oval right here, which I
labeled with a red five. So then I tried
to do the opposite and find the least
common letter. This combination only
showed up one time, so I assumed it was
the letter B. And I put this red two in
the bottom left to indicate that that
oval represented the second question.
And initially I thought I could label
these ovals one to five in a clockwise
fashion. So one red two three four red
five based on those two assumptions I
made. And I went down below and the
first four letters actually decoded
correctly. I got the word just. And
after that it started to go haywire and
I didn't see any real words. But it
bothered me that I felt like I was on
the right track with that. So I checked
out the letters that I had so far. I was
very confident in the letter E. I knew
the letter L was in the center. And then
I highlighted these letters in just JUS
T. And I noticed that all of these
letters actually have the same answer to
the second and the fourth questions. And
the second question was what I assumed
from the letter B here. So I realized
that I was very very close and I
happened to switch the second and fourth
circles. So when I swapped those here on
the ven diagram, that actually worked
out to decode the rest of the letters.
You could go for something more like
trial and error and try to guess other
vowels because I and you are in here and
they're going to be the eight and the
six. In any case, this is the final
decoded phrase. I actually noticed an
error in row six, column 6, where the
dog wagging its tail should not be
wagging its tail and this L should be
the letter E in adverb. And the message
says just a 100 exquisitly fuzzy puppies
can be viewed like an adverb, a number
from a Spielberg movie or a film by
Copa. And number in this case refers to
a musical number from the movie Westside
Story, which is somewhere and that fits
the other clues. They also did a good
job and made sure to put every letter
from A to Z somewhere in this grid so
that you really could solve this
systematically if you wanted to. Hence
the first part here, which is not
necessarily a clue. It's just to add the
letters X, Q, Z, J somewhere in this
grid. I have actually been in a pit
orchestra for Westside Story. It is a
lot of fun. Somewhere.
Puzzle number eight. I spent 100 hours
inside the pyramids. This one is just a
cross word in weird shape. a shape where
the words don't cross. This one is just
an uncross word in a completely normal
shape. Here are the solutions to four
crossword pyramids. The way this works
is you just start answering clues until
you see that a lot of them contain
similar letters. Here are the second
half of the clue answers. Resolution and
revolutions were the first clues I got
and they were right next to each other
and served as a good confirmation for
how to fill in these pyramids because
you can add a V to resolution to get all
of the letters in revolutions. Portion
and positron I actually made a mistake
early on because a proton I thought had
an electric charge of plus one E and
proton is also one letter off from
portion but posetron is the correct
answer. So that one took me a bit to
correct. Today I learned the word
orbiculate. And yes, Lar is a real
thing. One very neat design choice are
the four clues that say vowel that's not
U and that there are four answers each
of the other four vowels, A, E, I, and
O. And those serve as the tops of each
pyramid. Also, it definitely helps to
notice early on as you answer clues that
all of the answers are in alphabetical
order. So, when you're missing some, you
should be able to know from the
surrounding clues what letter your clue
starts with. Most likely, the answer to
this puzzle is actually a missing clue.
If you count them all up, there are only
43 and there are 11 rows in the pyramid.
Four pyramids makes 44 rows. So, around
highlighted in green here is the answer
to this puzzle as the missing word.
Puzzle number nine. Anything you can fit
in the circle, I'll pay for. This is
probably the most intimidating of the
first nine puzzles. And if you're
feeling like I have no idea what I'm
looking at and don't know what I would
do, you are not alone. I had the same
experience. But we can always play a
game of find the pattern. So the circle
on top has six red shaded triangles and
the circle on the bottom has two blue
shaded triangles. If I zoom in here on
the text that we've been given, the
letter in the second position has been
crossed out in blue and the letter in
the sixth position has been crossed out
in red. So, that's a pretty good
indicator that the number of triangles
shaded serves to cross out one of these
letters. And then we have this dot dot
dot that indicates we should be finding
more triangles. And that will cross out
more letters. And hopefully at the end,
we will see a hidden message pop out if
we cross out enough letters. Because
this puzzle resembles somebody's math
homework that they didn't want to do, I
went ahead and asked AI to help. But
first, I wanted to do some research so
that I had enough terms in my vocabulary
to talk about what it is we're working
with. And the shape we're looking at has
120 sides. It's called a distiocus
tricanted. And right at the end of the
intro on Wikipedia here, there is a
paragraph about projecting it into a
sphere, which means rounding all of the
edges and making this the shape we see
in the puzzle. And it talks about
defining 15 great circles. And I think
this was the ulterior motive of the
entire puzzle was to make sure that you
came across this term great circle,
which really just means drawing a
two-dimensional circle around a sphere
so that it's centered on the sphere. But
it'll be a long time before I come back
to this topic. It is needed to get the
first half of the final vault code after
you solve the first 100 puzzles. I did
not originally solve this puzzle myself.
I was happy to let somebody else do it,
but in preparing for this video, I went
to Claude Code and this was my first
prompt. I need help solving a math
problem. There is a sphere and its
surfaces split into 120 equally sized
spherical triangles. Assume the surface
area of a single triangle is one. I
would like to calculate the list of all
unique areas of triangles on the surface
of this sphere. Now, that sentence got
me in trouble because I said all unique
areas of triangles and it assumed I
meant areas made up of triangles, not
areas shaped like triangles. So, the
first response was all the areas, all of
them are possible. And then I said, "No,
triangles only." And then the last thing
it did was actually ask me a question
about great circles. So I was happy I
knew what those were. And then it turned
a bit, wrote some code, and out popped a
list of areas. Now, of course, I had no
way to know if these were the correct
areas until I went and solved the
puzzle. So I asked it to generate a
visualizer in Python. And here I have
the visualizer on the right side of the
screen. I currently have two triangles
selected, but I can click three and it
will show me an example of three
triangles making a larger triangle. And
then four and six is very easy to spot.
And seven. 15 is probably my favorite.
Look at that nice spiral around the
middle. All the way up to 42, which
looks like this. And the edges are
straight. There are only three edges.
And therefore, it is a triangle. So the
last thing to do was take that list of
areas and go ahead and cross out all of
the letters in those positions. And that
gave me the final clue phrase which is
homophone of wh i r l e d which is
world. So the answer to puzzle number
nine is w o r lld d world. As a quick
addendum to talk about the code in case
you're interested in writing your own
solution to this puzzle. The algorithm
isn't too hard. In this case it was just
the mathematical details that I wanted
to avoid. But essentially, you can look
up the equations of the 15 great circles
that form this shape in the puzzle and
write a loop that iterates over every
combination of three great circles and
then calculates the area of the triangle
formed by those great circles. And by
the end, you'll have a set of unique
areas. There are just some tricky
details along the way such as you can't
select parallel great circles. I don't
know if that's the correct term here,
but what I mean by that is you can see
these pentagons and in the center of
those pentagons, there is an
intersection of five great circles. So,
if you pick any of those three, they
form these long sort of crescent shapes,
but they never actually form any
triangles. For posterity, here are some
of the tools I personally used to solve
these puzzles. The first is word plays,
my favorite cross word solver. It has
more ads these days than it used to, but
it's a great database and can even help
with cryptic crosswords at times. Next
is Neutramatic, which is a word finding
pattern matching tool created by the
great Dan Egnore. This tool has somewhat
of a learning curve, but it's very
robust. Amazing for help with anagrams
and puzzles like number three with the
TV shows and number eight where each
layer of the pyramid scrambled the
previous letters. Dan also maintains the
puzzle hunt calendar where if you liked
these nine puzzles, you can find a
schedule of upcoming competitive events
where you're guaranteed to see a whole
lot more puzzles very much like these.
Next up is Litcape, my backup word
finder. This website is very easy to
use, has some different word lists to
search and multiple different tools. The
words containing only tool was very
useful for the TV shows. All I had to do
was set the length to two letters less
than I had in order to find some of the
trickier words for that puzzle. Last, I
want to mention Simon Taam's portable
puzzle collection. This site has plenty
of fun games and if you're looking to
challenge your logic skills, you might
recognize some guests. also known as
mastermind mind sweeper right below that
and the reason I am mentioning it for
this video is tense from puzzle number
Thanks.